[
    {
        "id": "q1",
        "question": "(true false) A cheese is a cheese",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "answer": "True",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": 10,
        "weight" : 0.10,    "index_answer": 1,
        "type":  "tf"
    },
    {
        "id": "q2",
        "question": "(multiple choice) A cheese is a cheese",
        "options": ["yes", "no", "no", "no"],
        "answer": "yes",
        "difficulty": 1,    "index_answer": 1,
        "points": 20,
        "weight" : 0.10, "type":  "mc"

    },
    {
        "id": "q3",
        "question": "(short coding) A cheese is a cheese",
        "options": [
            "cheese",
            "no cheese",
            "no cheese",
            "no cheese"
        ],
        "answer": "cheese",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": 30,
        "weight" : 0.10,    "index_answer": 1,
        "type":  "sc"
    },
    {
        "id": "q4",
        "question": "(long coding) A cheese is a cheese",
        "options": ["yes", "no"],
        "answer": "yes",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "points": 40,    "index_answer": 1,
        "weight" : 0.10,
        "type":  "lc"
    },
    {
        "id": "q5",
        "question": "(true false) A cheese is a cheese",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "answer": "True",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": 10,
        "weight" : 0.20,
        "type":  "tf",    "index_answer": 1
    },
    {
        "id": "q6",
        "question": "(multiple choice) A cheese is a cheese",
        "options": ["yes", "no", "no", "no"],
        "answer": "yes",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": 20,
        "weight" : 0.20, "type":  "mc",
            "index_answer": 1
    },
    {
        "id": "q7",
        "question": "(short coding) A cheese is a cheese",
        "options": [
            "cheese",
            "no cheese",
            "no chesee",
            "no chesee"
        ],
        "answer": "cheese",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": 30,
        "weight" : 0.20,
        "type":  "sc",
            "index_answer": 1
    },
    {
        "id": "q8",
        "question": "(long coding) A cheese is a cheese",
        "options": ["yes", "no"],
        "answer": "yes",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "points": 40,
        "weight" : 0.20,
        "type":  "lc",
            "index_answer": 1
    },

            {
        "id": "q9",
        "question": "(true false) A cheese is a cheese",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "answer": "True",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": 10,
                    "index_answer": 1,
        "weight" : 0.30,
        "type":  "tf"
    },
    {
        "id": "q10",
        "question": "(multiple choice) A cheese is a cheese",
        "options": ["yes", "no", "no", "no"],
        "answer": "yes",
        "difficulty": 3,
            "index_answer": 1,
        "points": 20,
        "weight" : 0.30, "type":  "mc"

    },
    {
        "id": "q11",
        "question": "(short coding) A cheese is a cheese",
        "options": [
            "cheese",
            "no cheese",
            "no cheese",
            "no cheese"
        ],
        "answer": "cheese",
            "index_answer": 1,
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": 30,
        "weight" : 0.30,
        "type":  "sc"
    },
    {
        "id": "q12",
        "question": "(long coding) A cheese is a cheese",
        "options": ["yes", "no"],
        "answer": "yes",
        "index_answer": 1,
        "difficulty": 3,
        "points": 40,
        "weight" : 0.30,
        "type":  "lc"
    }
]